[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section seven
您好，欢迎来到第七节
of lesson one.
第一课
In this section we're going to look at some of the new methods that have been
在本节中，我们将研究一些新的方法
added in JDK 8
在JDK 8中添加
to the standard class libraries where,
到标准的类库，
because the parameters are on functional interfaces,
因为参数在功能接口上，
you can use Lambda expressions to express the behavior
您可以使用Lambda表达式来表达行为
that you want from these methods. The first of these
这些方法想要的。这些中的第一个
is in the the Iterable interface. What this means is that
在Iterable界面中。这意味着
if you have a class now which implements the Iterable interface
如果您现在有一个实现Iterable接口的类
it will have a new method called forEach
它将有一个名为forEach的新方法
available to it and the forEach method
适用于它和forEach方法
takes a consumer as a parameter. As we can see from the example here
将消费者作为参数。从这里的例子中我们可以看到
what we can now do is have myList, which is a list of type string,
现在我们可以做的是myList，它是字符串类型的列表，
and then we can say that for each element
然后我们可以说每个元素
in that collection we want to print out its value.
在该集合中，我们要打印出其价值。
Rather than having to construct an explicit loop ourselves in doing for
不必为此自己构造一个显式循环
over the collection and have a body of the for loop
在集合上并具有for循环的主体
to do whatever we want do we can use the Lambda expression
做我们想做的事，我们可以使用Lambda表达式
to say what it is we want to do in each
说说我们想在每个地方做什么
iteration of the elements that we have in the collection.
集合中元素的迭代。
Here we just want to print out lines, print out the
在这里，我们只想打印出行，打印出
the elements of the collection and, again, we can do that in
集合的元素，同样，我们可以在
a simplified form using the equivalent method reference.
使用等效方法参考的简化形式。
The collection interface
采集界面
has had a very useful new method added to it,
已经添加了非常有用的新方法，
which is removeif, and removeif
分别是removeif和removeif
takes a predicate as a parameter. What this allows us to do
以谓词为参数。这允许我们做什么
is for a particular collection, which in this case is example is a
用于特定集合，在这种情况下，示例是
list of type string, we can specify which
类型字符串列表，我们可以指定
elements of that collection we want to remove based
我们要删除的集合元素
on whether the predicate we use returns true or false.
是否使用谓词返回true或false。
In the example what I'm trying to do is remove
在该示例中，我要删除的是
any elements from this list of strings, which are zero characters in length.
此字符串列表中的任何元素，其长度为零个字符。
It's very simple, we just say where
很简单，我们只说哪里
the length of the string is zero then
字符串的长度为零，则
those will be removed. Again, it’s the ability to
这些将被删除。同样，这是
eliminate all the extra work that we would have to do to have an explicit loop
消除了为实现显式循环而要做的所有额外工作
where we have to go through the collection ourselves, test whether the
我们必须亲自检查集合的地方，测试是否
length of the string is zero and then remove it explicitly from the collection
字符串的长度为零，然后将其从集合中显式删除
all this is now achieved in one line of code.
所有这些现在都可以通过一行代码实现。
The list interface, which is obviously a subclass of the
列表接口，显然是它的子类
collection interface, has also had a new
采集界面，也有了新的
method added to it. In this case it's called replaceAll
方法添加到它。在这种情况下，它称为replaceAll
and that takes a UnaryOperator.
这需要一个UnaryOperator。
If you remember back to the earlier part of the lesson where we talked about
如果您还记得我们之前讨论的课程的较早部分
the interfaces in the
中的接口
java.util.function package. Again, what we can do here is take our
java.util.function包。同样，我们在这里可以做的就是
list of strings
字符串列表
and what we want to do is replace all of the contents
而我们要做的是替换所有内容
of that collection in terms of those strings
那些字符串的集合
with strings that have been converted in some way
用某种方式转换的字符串
using that UnaryOperator. In this case, we
使用该UnaryOperator。在这种情况下，我们
want to convert all of the strings to upper case and
想要将所有字符串都转换为大写，并且
we can do that with Lambda expression where we say s is the parameter
我们可以用Lambda表达式做到这一点，我们说s是参数
s.toUpperCase is the body of the expression.
s.toUpperCase是表达式的主体。
We can use the equivalent method reference
我们可以使用等效方法参考
where, if you remember from earlier in the lesson, we use the type
如果您还记得本课程前面的内容，则使用
of the parameter, s, as our class,
参数s作为我们的类，
string and we use to UpperCase
字符串，我们使用UpperCase
as the name of the method. That will give us the equivalent
作为方法的名称。那将给我们等效
of the the code above.
上面的代码。
The list interface also has another method added to it, which is sort
列表接口还添加了另一种方法，即排序
and this is really a kind of replacement
这真的是一种替代
for an existing method which is Collections.sort,
对于现有方法Collections.sort，
where you can pass in a list and a comparator, but this way
您可以在其中传递列表和比较器，但是这种方式
it's built into the list interface, so you can call sort directly
它内置在列表界面中，因此您可以直接调用sort
on the list that you've got rather than having to call a static method on the Collections
在您拥有的列表上，而不必在集合上调用静态方法
utility class. Now, again, with my list of strings we can simply call sort
实用程序类。现在，再次使用我的字符串列表，我们可以简单地调用sort
and we can pass in a comparator. We've seen the comparator used before.
我们可以传入一个比较器我们已经看到了以前使用的比较器。
We’re passing in two parameters, x and y,
我们传入两个参数x和y
and remember that the compiler can use type inference.
并记住编译器可以使用类型推断。
It knows that list of type string so it knows that the comparator will be of type
它知道字符串类型的列表，所以它知道比较器将是类型
string,
串，
so x and y, which are arguments to the comparator must be of type string.
因此，作为比较器参数的x和y必须为string类型。
The body of the comparator, compare method
比较器的主体，比较方法
is to simply return the difference in length between the strings,
就是简单地返回字符串之间的长度差，
which means that what we’ll actually be doing is sorting the strings by length.
这意味着我们实际上要做的是按长度对字符串进行排序。
The
的
logger class. This is a quite a common problem
记录器类。这是一个很普遍的问题
we see with logging and there aren't many other situations like this as well,
我们看到了日志记录，也没有其他类似的情况，
but
但
logging is a very good example. What I'm doing
日志记录就是一个很好的例子。我在做什么
is I want to log a certain type of message
我是否要记录某种类型的消息
and the way that that message needs to be generated is using this
而需要生成该消息的方式就是使用这个
method called createComplexMessage. I'm using the
方法称为createComplexMessage。我正在使用
finest message in the logging
日志中最好的消息
API to say that I only want to record these messages
API表示我只想记录这些消息
when the logging level is set to the very finest
当日志记录级别设置为最佳时
level. That's fine, but the problem we have
水平。很好，但是我们有问题
is that createComplexMessage must be called
是必须调用createComplexMessage
every time, even when it's not required.
每次，即使不需要。
if I set the logging level to be info or warning
如果我将日志记录级别设置为info或warning
then, when the complex message is created and passed to that method
然后，当创建复杂消息并将其传递给该方法时
the finest method will say ah, level is not set to
最好的方法会说啊，水平未设置为
finest, so we don't need to use this message so we just ignore it. But
最好，因此我们不需要使用此消息，因此我们将其忽略。但
createComplexMessage has been called.
createComplexMessage已被调用。
If, for the sake of argument, that takes five seconds to create the complicated message,
如果为了论证而花费五秒钟来创建复杂的消息，
then every time we call this we’re being delayed by five seconds, regardless
然后每次我们称此为延迟五秒，无论
of whether this is used or not. This is in some ways like Heisenberg's
是否使用它。这在某种程度上就像海森堡的
uncertainty principle applied to software.
不确定性原理适用于软件。
Now Heisenberg's uncertainty principle is from quantum mechanics and
现在海森堡的不确定性原理来自量子力学和
says that the act of observing something changes what you're observing
说观察事物的行为会改变您正在观察的事物
but it has the same kind of effect in terms of what we do with our logging
但就我们的采伐而言，它具有相同的效果
messages.
消息。
To make this a lot easier and to avoid these problems
为了使这更容易并避免出现这些问题
in the logger class we’ve now added new versions of each of
在logger类中，我们现在添加了每个版本的新版本
the logging APIs, so the finest, fine,
记录API，所以最好的
warning, info, and so on which take a supplier
警告，信息等，这些信息会带给供应商
as an argument. Again, remember back, that a supplier
作为争论。再说一遍，记得供应商
is a functional interface, has one abstract method
是一个功能接口，具有一种抽象方法
and we can use Lambda expression to represent that.
我们可以使用Lambda表达式来表示。
That means that by changing our code
这意味着通过更改我们的代码
very slightly we can have a big impact on performance
我们可以对性能产生很大的影响
Now, what we're doing is simply changing
现在，我们正在做的只是改变
the call to finest. Rather than passing createComplexMessage,
呼吁最好。而不是传递createComplexMessage，
we pass a Lambda expression, which is the
我们传递一个Lambda表达式，即
supplier. In this case it takes no arguments,
供应商。在这种情况下，不需要任何参数，
so the left hand side is empty brackets. The right hand side is
因此左侧是空括号。右边是
to create our complex message. Now what's gonna happen is we’re
创建我们的复杂信息。现在要发生的是我们
going to pass this Lambda expression to finest
最好通过这个Lambda表达式
and then only if finest needs it will it actually
然后只有最需要的时候才可以
use this supplier and call the appropriate method
使用此供应商并调用适当的方法
and then create the complex message. The great thing is that
然后创建复杂的消息。很棒的是
what we’re doing now is passing behavior
我们现在正在做的是传递行为
rather than value. We’re passing a description
而不是价值。我们正在传递说明
of how to create the message, not the actual message.
如何创建消息，而不是实际消息。
That way if we want to ignore it, rather than ignoring the message
这样，如果我们想忽略它，而不是忽略消息
which has been created by a very long process we’re
这是经过很长的过程创建的
just ignoring the description, which takes no time at all.
只是忽略了描述，这完全不需要时间。
Much much better.
好多了。
This is also the kind of thing you can use in your own code if you have a
如果您有自己的代码，也可以在自己的代码中使用
kind of conditional situation where you don't know whether
你不知道是否有条件的情况
the value that’s being passed is going to be used or not. Passing a way of
传递的值将不被使用。通过一种方式
how to construct that message could be much more efficient. To summarize section
如何构造该消息可能会更有效率。总结部分
seven, then,
那七
there are a number of new methods in JDK 8,
JDK 8中有许多新方法
which provide you the ability to use Lambda expressions
这使您能够使用Lambda表达式
as parameters and most of these are based around
作为参数，其中大多数基于
avoiding having to do a lot of extra loop constructs,
避免进行很多额外的循环构造，
although not always because, if you think of the
尽管并非总是如此，因为如果您想到
logging API what this allows us to do
记录API，这允许我们做什么
is to eliminate some of the overhead performance that we get
是为了消除我们获得的一些间接性能
by always passing values. By passing
通过始终传递值。通过传递
behavior to describe how we want to create these messages or
用来描述我们如何创建这些消息的行为或
how we want to do something this can really help us to improve
我们想要做些什么，这确实可以帮助我们改善
the performance of our application.
我们应用程序的性能。
That is the end of the first lesson and what I’d just like doing now is to
第一节课到此结束，我现在想做的是
spend a couple minutes summarizing what we've covered
花一些时间总结一下我们所涵盖的内容
in this lesson and what you've learnt so far. We’ve talked about Lambda
在本课程中以及您到目前为止所学到的知识。我们已经讨论过Lambda
expressions
表达
and the key thing that I really want to get across
和我真正想传达的关键
from this lesson is that Lambda expressions provide you with a simple
本课的内容是Lambda表达式为您提供了一个简单的方法
way
方式
to pass behavior as parameter. Rather than always passing
将行为作为参数传递。而不是总是过去
values we can pass description of how to create something
我们可以传递有关如何创建事物的描述的值
in terms of that parameter. When we can use Lambda
就该参数而言。什么时候可以使用Lambda
expressions is wherever we have a functional interface.
表达式是我们拥有功能性接口的任何地方。
Remember a functional interface is one that has a single
请记住，一个功能接口只有一个
abstract method and the Lambda expression,
抽象方法和Lambda表达式，
although it's not associated with a class, provides
尽管它与类无关，但提供了
an implementation of the abstract method that is
抽象方法的实现是
contained in that functional interface. We have
包含在该功能界面中。我们有
shorthand forms for certain types of Lambda expressions where
某些类型的Lambda表达式的简写形式，其中
we're using a single method in terms of the Lambda body
就Lambda主体而言，我们使用的是一种方法
then we can use method references. If we’re using a constructor
然后我们可以使用方法引用。如果我们使用构造函数
as a single statement in our Lambda
作为我们Lambda中的一个声明
expression we can use a constructor reference.
表达式我们可以使用构造函数引用。
As we've just seen there are a number of useful new methods
正如我们刚刚看到的，有许多有用的新方法
in JDK 8 that can use Lambdas and these are ones
在可以使用Lambda的JDK 8中，这些是
outside of the streams API, which we’re going to cover
在流API之外，我们将介绍
in the next lesson. And that is the end
在下一课中。到此为止
of the first lesson.
第一堂课